<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<people xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance">
	<person>
		<firstname>Curtis</firstname>
		<lastname>Howell</lastname>
		<class>Senior</class>
		<major1>Business Administration</major1>
		<concentration1>Entrepreneurship</concentration1>
		<major2>Informatics</major2>
		<bio>Curtis is pursuing degrees in Informatics and Business Administration with a focus in Entrepreneurship. He keeps busy with a number of volunteer activities including serving student representative on the Student Technology Fee Committee for the University of Washington and as the IT Manager for Montlake Consulting Group. Last summer Curtis interned as a Program Manager with Microsoft Office before crossing the pond to study abroad for a semester at Copenhagen Business School. In his spare time, Curtis enjoys tennis, golf, softball, skiing and competing in triathlons.</bio>
		<position>Managing Partner</position>
		<projects>King County Metro</projects>
		<linkedin>http://linkedin.com/in/curtisjhowell</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>CurtisH.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Cory</firstname>
		<lastname>Slater Scancella</lastname>
		<class>Senior</class>
		<major1>Business</major1>
		<concentration1>Accounting</concentration1>
		<bio>Cory is a junior majoring in Business with an Accounting focus. He is currently the Portfolio Implementation intern at Russell Investments, where he works on the trading floor, within the Investment Division. Past work experience includes managing and operating his own highly profitable painting business the summer after his freshman year, employing a full-time crew of employees. He will likely obtain his CPA before, or shortly after, entering the workforce. Additionally, Cory wants to get an MBA after a few years of experience in the professional world. 

With the help of MCG, Cory has realized that the management consulting industry is aligned perfectly with his passions and abilities, and he hopes to enter it upon completion of his degree. This past year in MCG, Cory had the opportunity to work with two clients, one of which was Seattle-based retailer Nordstroms, Inc., which culminated in a presentation of findings and actionable recommendations to the V.P. of full-line stores and V.P. of Strategy, among others. The other project surrounded a concept called Transit Oriented Development (TOD) for the Seattle transit organization, King County Metro. Cory is currently managing a follow-up project with King County Metro in Autumn 2011 and Winter 2012. </bio>
		<position>Managing Partner</position>
		<projects>King County Metro, Nordstrom</projects>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/pub/cory-slater-scancella/32/ab1/507</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>CoryS.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Evan</firstname>
		<lastname>Griffith</lastname>
		<class>Senior</class>
		<major1>Business Administration</major1>
		<concentration1>Finance &amp; Information Systems</concentration1>
		<bio>Evan is a junior majoring in Business Administration with concentrations in Finance and Information Systems. He is currently the Marketing Director for Advertising Club UW, a student-run advertising agency. He is also active in case competitions, and recently placed first in the Diversity in Business Case Competition. Evan will be joining Amazon.com in the Spring as a Financial Analyst Intern for six months. After graduation, he hopes to pursue a career in Management Consulting, and go on to obtain an MBA. Evan is currently staffed on his first engagement with MCG working with King County Metro.</bio>
		<position>Junior Partner</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/in/evancgriffith</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>EvanG.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Eric</firstname>
		<lastname>Bauer</lastname>
		<class>Senior</class>
		<major1>Business Administration</major1>
		<concentration1>Accounting</concentration1>
		<major2>Business Administration</major2>
		<bio>Eric Bauer is in his 3rd year of study at the University of Washington, and will complete his degree in Business Administration in 2013. He is pursuing options in accounting and information systems, which reflect his interests in technology and financial analysis. Eric has substantial entrepreneurial experience with small consumer service companies. He also has professional experience with StudyManager, which provides cloud-based software used to track clinical trials, and Merrill Lynch. His extracurricular interests include health and fitness, cooking, and photography.</bio>
		<position>Manager</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/pub/eric-bauer/14/265/65</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>EricB.jpg</imagethumb>
		<concentration2>Information Systems</concentration2>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Suparno</firstname>
		<lastname>Chakrabarti</lastname>
		<class>Junior</class>
		<major1>Applied &amp; Computational Math Sciences</major1>
		<concentration1>Operations Research</concentration1>
		<major2>Informatics</major2>
		<bio>Suparno is a junior in Applied Computational Math Sciences and Informatics. His work experiences include working for Mountain Plus Outdoor gear as a web developer, he sits on the Board of Trustees for the University Bookstore, as well as the Finance and Budget Committee for the Associated Students of the University of Washington. He is currently a Resident Adviser in Lander Hall. Suparno hopes to earn a Masters degree in Applied Mathematics or Computer Science.</bio>
		<position>Manager</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=91420225&amp;trk=tab_pro</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>SuparnoC.jpg</imagethumb>
		<concentration2>Information Architecture</concentration2>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Adam</firstname>
		<lastname>Greenberg</lastname>
		<class>Senior</class>
		<major1>Business Administration</major1>
		<concentration1>Finance</concentration1>
		<major2>Business Administration</major2>
		<bio>Adam is a senior majoring in Business Administration with a double concentration in Finance and Entrepreneurship. He is also just short of an Environmental Studies minor. He grew up in San Francisco and moved to Seattle to attend the University of Washington. His work experience includes financial analyst at Amazon.com and CFO of The MS Children's Book non profit organization. Past consulting experiences include social media, graphic user interfaces, and financial analysis. This past summer he interned at Asset Management Strategies Inc. and studied abroad in Italy. In his spare time, he enjoys tennis, photography, volunteering, and traveling. </bio>
		<position>Manager</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/in/adamgreenberg1</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>AdamG.jpg</imagethumb>
		<concentration2>Entrepreneurship</concentration2>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Jim</firstname>
		<lastname>Inoue</lastname>
		<class>Senior</class>
		<major1>Computer Science</major1>
		<major2>Business Administration</major2>
		<bio>Jim Inoue is currently a senior studying both Computer Science and Business Finance. As a freshmen he worked for a local startup as a marketing director. The next two summers, he interned at Microsoft as a product manager implementing Information Technology Infrastructure Library (ITIL) processes and then in Microsoft's online advertising division as a program manager, where he developed an internal web tool used by partners in the organization across the globe. He plans to continue to develop his technical background at Amazon this winter and at a software company down in the bay area during the summer time. At school, he has held multiple leadership roles including his current role as an officer of Association for Computing Machinery (ACM) UW. While unsure what he will pursue after he graduates, Jim would ultimately like to explore his entrepreneurial interests in the tech industry. Jim enjoys playing the piano and biking and most recently completed the 200 mile bike ride from Seattle to Portland.</bio>
		<position>Manager</position>
		<projects>King County Metro</projects>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/in/jinoue3</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>JimI.jpg</imagethumb>
		<concentration2>Finance</concentration2>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Munir</firstname>
		<lastname>Nanjee</lastname>
		<class>Senior</class>
		<major1>Business Administration</major1>
		<concentration1>Accounting and Information Systems</concentration1>
		<bio>Munir is a junior majoring in Business Administration with a focus on Accounting and Information System. He has made a name for himself on campus by being involved with multiple activities and taking leadership roles. He is currently the president of Sigma Beta Rho Fraternity and co-founder of an activist group on campus. He was also on the executive board for his hall council which was awarded top residence hall community in the Western U.S. by the Pacific Affiliate of College and University Residence Hall (PACURH). Last summer he interned at Mercer and consulted for Sunkist, Value Click, and Children's Hospital in the areas of Health and Benefits. He has a passion for consulting and financial analysis. </bio>
		<position>Manager</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/pub/munir-nanjee/16/547/46b</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>MunirN.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Michael</firstname>
		<lastname>Abboud</lastname>
		<class>Junior</class>
		<major1>Computer Science</major1>
		<major2>Electrical Enginerring</major2>
		<bio>Michael Abboud is a sophomore studying Computer Science and Electrical Engineering. He loves playing sports like football and basketball, attending as many Husky athletics events as he can, and staying involved. Previous experience includes working with the ASUW Special Appropriations Committee and the Finance and Budget Committee dealing with issuing grants and loans to registered student organizations on campus.  Michael plans on receiving his MBA at some point in his career. While he is one of the younger members of MCG, Michael looks forward to the experience with real world issues, and the opportunity to work with a extremely bright and motivated group of future leaders.</bio>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<imagethumb>MichaelA.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Rich</firstname>
		<lastname>An</lastname>
		<class>Senior</class>
		<major1>Business Administration</major1>
		<major2>Electrical Engineering</major2>
		<bio>Rich is currently a senior working on a double degree in Business Administration and Electrical Engineering.  He is studying general business at Foster, while specializing in embedded computer systems and integrated circuits under the Electrical Engineering department.  In the summer following his Junior year, he worked on testing radio and wireless hardware as a Hardware Engineering Intern at Itron, a smart-grid solutions company located in Liberty Lake, WA.  This summer, he will work as an Design Automation Intern in the microprocessor development group at Intel, where he can apply his engineering knowledge and expertise.  After he graduates, Rich plans to develop a career in either engineering research and development, or technology consulting.  In his free time, Rich enjoys playing basketball, taking pictures, and reading about the latest technology.</bio>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=126404325</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>RichA.jpg</imagethumb>
		<concentration2>Embedded Computing Systems</concentration2>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Kyle</firstname>
		<lastname>Bartlow</lastname>
		<class>Senior</class>
		<major1>Business Administration</major1>
		<concentration1>Information Systems</concentration1>
		<bio>Kyle is a junior majoring in Business Administration with a concentration in Information Systems. He is an experienced case competitor and in his first two years at UW has presented over six cases in a variety of industries.  These competitions have included presentations to faculty, professionals, and executives of local businesses. Kyle’s biggest competition accomplishment to date was placing in the final four of the 2011 Foster Global Business Case Competition, at which 12 teams from 10 different countries were in attendance. This is his first year with MCG and he is excited to bring what he has learned to help local companies.  This summer Kyle will be taking an internship with Triage Consulting Group in San Francisco. In his free time he likes to spend time in the outdoors, with friends, as well as learning about investing and personal finance. </bio>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/pub/kyle-bartlow/22/a07/2a3</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>KyleB.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Wuen</firstname>
		<lastname>Ong</lastname>
		<class>Junior</class>
		<major1>Business Administration</major1>
		<bio>Wuen is a sophomore pursuing a degree in Business Administration and intends to earn a Certificate of International Studies in Business. With a passion for teamwork, she has participated in both local and international case competitions and placed on finalist teams three times within the past year. Wuen is currently the Vice President of Marketing &amp; Information Management at AIESEC Seattle, a local chapter of the largest student-run organization in the world, and additionally serves on the Executive Committee for the Lavin Entrepreneurial Program, helping to involve fellow students in the burgeoning startup community of Seattle. Outside of school and student organizations, Wuen enjoys being with friends and family, playing various stringed instruments, singing, and dancing.</bio>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/in/wuenong</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>WuenO.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Tim</firstname>
		<lastname>Tan</lastname>
		<class>Senior</class>
		<major1>Business Administration</major1>
		<concentration1>Customer</concentration1>
		<major2>Informatics</major2>
		<bio>Tim is a junior studying Business Administration and Informatics. Currently, he works as the Managing Director for TEDxUofW and as the Design Intern for UW Marketing. His previous experience includes Assistant Director for UW Leaders, Washington DECA State President, and the Operations Team at REI. This past Fall, Tim was recently selected as a Mary Gates Leadership Scholar. A former competitive swimmer, curious cellist, active event photographer, and voracious reader, Tim keeps himself occupied with a diverse mix of hobbies. When he graduates, Tim hopes to work for a technology company and potentially launch his own startup. </bio>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/in/itstimtime</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>TimT.jpg</imagethumb>
		<concentration2>Custom</concentration2>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Cameron</firstname>
		<lastname>Chinn</lastname>
		<class>Junior</class>
		<major1>Business Administration</major1>
		<concentration1>Finance &amp; Information Systems</concentration1>
		<bio>Cameron is a junior majoring in Business Administration with a focus in Finance and Information Systems. His work experience includes working in the areas of microfinance, financial services, and insurance. For the past year, Cameron has worked at Liberty Mutual as a Product Analyst Intern and this Summer will transition to Amazon.com as a Financial Analyst Intern for six months.  He is also active in case competitions, having won the Ernst &amp; Young/UMCA Case Competition and organized the Global Business Case Competition and the Wells Fargo Case Competition.  In his free time he likes to spend time on the golf course or on the ski slopes.  After obtaining a Masters of Science in Information Systems, he hopes to pursue a career with a technology firm and create his own business.</bio>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/pub/cameron-chinn/20/7a6/401</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>CameronC.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Tomoki</firstname>
		<lastname>Lam</lastname>
		<class>Junior</class>
		<major1>Business Administration</major1>
		<concentration1>Finance &amp; Information Systems</concentration1>
		<bio>Tomoki is a Junior majoring in Business Administration with focuses in Finance and Information Systems. He has worked at Summerfield Commercial in the past as a real estate finance researcher and has also participated in a few case competitions. He is also currently the treasurer of Psi Upsilon and is working at Amazon this summer and fall as a financial analyst. Tomoki hopes to pursue something within the financial field and obtain an MBA after a few years of work experience. He is looking forward to working with all the talented members of MCG and gaining real world business experiences to grow his financial skill sets.</bio>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/in/tomokilam</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>TomokiL.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Curtis</firstname>
		<lastname>Lan</lastname>
		<class>Senior</class>
		<major1>Business Administration</major1>
		<concentration1>Marketing, Finance</concentration1>
		<bio>Curtis is a junior majoring in Marketing and Finance at the Foster School of Business. His work experience includes starting his own social travel network company where he acts primarily as a strategy analyst. He is currently interning at Search Engine Optimist where he analyzes the internet presence of clients. This summer, he will be interning at Microsoft as an Associate Product Manager Intern.  His extracurricular interests include playing the cello, tennis, and reading.</bio>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/in/curtislan</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>CurtisL.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Quinn</firstname>
		<lastname>Lawlor</lastname>
		<class>Junior</class>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<imagethumb>QuinnL.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Michael</firstname>
		<lastname>Manolides</lastname>
		<class>Junior</class>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<imagethumb>MichaelM.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Jonathan</firstname>
		<lastname>Matson</lastname>
		<class>Senior</class>
		<major1>Business Administration</major1>
		<concentration1>International Business &amp; Finance</concentration1>
		<bio>Jonathan is a junior majoring in Business Administration with a focus in finance. He is also working to complete the Certificate of International Studies in Business (CISB) program in the french language track, and plans to complete a semester abroad in Lyon, France, beginning Winter 2014. As a freshman at UW he joined in the re-founding of the Alpha Delta Phi fraternity, and has since held numerous leadership roles as the house subsequently grew from 20 to 80+ members. He is passionate about helping people,  which has led him to volunteer with several  organizations over the years including Dream Project, the Hand &amp; Heart, and Big Brothers Big Sisters. He is currently a team and board member of the Washington Boxing Team, and in his free time he enjoys being with friends and family, outdoor activities, and traveling. After finishing college Jonathan plans to join the workforce to gain some experience and then return to school for a graduate degree in business or law.</bio>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/pub/jonathan-matson/26/294/329</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>JonathanM.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Cameron</firstname>
		<lastname>Najmabadi</lastname>
		<class>Junior</class>
		<major1>Applied Mathematics</major1>
		<major2>Economics</major2>
		<bio>Cameron is a sophomore majoring in Applied Mathematics and Economics, with an emphasis in finance. His work experiences include working for UBS as a private wealth management intern. On his spare time Cameron enjoys reading about capital markets and playing an active role in the Husky Traders Student Investmend Fund. Cameron hopes to earn a Masters degree in business administration.</bio>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/pub/cameron-najmabadi/38/850/701</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>CameronN.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Chaitrali</firstname>
		<lastname>Pimparkar</lastname>
		<class>Senior</class>
		<major1>Informatics</major1>
		<concentration1>Information Security and Assurance</concentration1>
		<bio>Chaitrali Pimparkar is a junior at the University of Washington, pursuing a degree in Informatics with a focus in Information Security and Assurance. Her passion for bridging the gap between people, information, and technology has led to her involvement with iSchool Leadership as the Director of Outreach for IUGA, as well as her service on the Informatics Program Committee. She currently works as a Technology Assistant at the Foster School of Business, managing BlackBoard technologies and MediaSite applications. Chaitrali’s consulting experiences include working as an IT Consultant with UW-IT, and leading a systems analysis project with Microsoft Finance. With an interest in risk and assurance, she is in the process of receiving her Certificate of Information Security through the Master of Science in Information Management Program at the Information School. Previously, Chaitrali had the opportunity to intern with Vertafore as an Associate Software Engineer, and contributed to the development of an Automation Test Framework for Agency Management Systems. Aside from academics; she is the President of her dance team, and has an affinity for travelling, painting, and learning new languages. Starting in June 2012, Chaitrali is looking forward to interning with Deloitte &amp; Touche as an Advisory Consultant in Technology Risk.</bio>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=102054137&amp;trk=tab_pro</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>ChaitraliP.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Jet</firstname>
		<lastname>Saini</lastname>
		<class>Junior</class>
		<major1>Business Administration</major1>
		<concentration1>Finance &amp; Information systems</concentration1>
		<bio>Jet is a sophomore majoring in Business Administration – Finance and Information Systems with a Dance Minor. He is currently the Marketing Chair for Ascend UW, helping promote Asian leadership in the business community. He spent this past summer interning as a Project Analyst with the Federal Reserve Bank of San Francisco will be an Advisory Consultant at his internship with Deloitte and Touche this summer. Jet has also been a hip-hop dancer for 2 years now and when he’s not on stage you can find him at the nearest court playing volleyball.</bio>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/in/gurjits</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>JetS.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Catriona</firstname>
		<lastname>Scott</lastname>
		<class>Senior</class>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<imagethumb>CatrionaS.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Brennen</firstname>
		<lastname>Smith</lastname>
		<class>Junior</class>
		<major1>Informatics</major1>
		<concentration1>Information Architecture</concentration1>
		<bio>Brennen is a junior in Informatics focusing on Information Architecture. His work experiences range from developing large scale payroll and logistics systems to security auditing for healthcare providers. He is currently working for the Foster School of Business as an IT specialist and Janicki Industries for advanced network design and deployment. He is also in the process of starting a company, Fathom Computers, which specializes in developing advanced marine navigational systems. Brennen is a three time recipient of the NASA Space Grant, a member of UW's Honors Program, and a Washington Aerospace Scholar. He currently holds advanced ABYC certifications and was on the North American Junior Olympic Team for alpine ski racing.</bio>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<imagethumb>BrennenS.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Nashua</firstname>
		<lastname>Springberry</lastname>
		<class>Junior</class>
		<major1>Business with CISB (Chinese Track)</major1>
		<concentration1>Finance</concentration1>
		<bio>Nashua is a Junior majoring in Business with concentration in Finance. He is also pursuing a Certificate of International Studies in Business (CISB) on the Chinese track. His work experience includes working for Eastern Washington Universities Business Resource Center, various political campaigns, as an intern at Pacific Capital Resource Group, and starting this summer he'll be a financial analyst intern at Amazon. At the University of Washington he has also won both the PwC and KPMG case competitions. Including being selected out of 65 different winning teams from universities across the country to compete at Nationals. The first team in UW history to be so honored. Nashua is also on the Associated Students of the University of Washington's Finance and Budget Committee and a associate member of the Husky Traders Investment Fund. This is Nashua's first year at MCG and he looks forward to making it a great one.</bio>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<imagethumb>NashuaS.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Maia</firstname>
		<lastname>Szafer</lastname>
		<class>Senior</class>
		<major1>Business Administration</major1>
		<concentration1>Accounting</concentration1>
		<major2>Computer Science</major2>
		<bio>Maia is pursuing degrees in Computer Science and Business Administration, with a focus in Accounting. She has been involved in the community as a teaching assistant for the UW's Department of Computer Science and Engineering and looks forward to contributing to Montlake Consulting Group in the upcoming years.</bio>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/pub/maia-szafer/27/5a3/981</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>MaiaS.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
	<person>
		<firstname>Mason</firstname>
		<lastname>Wrolstad</lastname>
		<class>Senior</class>
		<major1>Informatics</major1>
		<concentration1>Information Architecture</concentration1>
		<bio>Mason is a junior majoring in Informatics with an Information Architecture focus. He is working for Boeing this upcoming summer as an Information Analyst at the Bellevue campus. This includes working with a wide variety of people to solve desktop solutions. In the past Mason has worked at Synrad Inc, a world leader in laser manufacturing, as a information tech. Through time in the Informatics program, Mason has obtained several technical skills and hopes to use this technical knowledge to enter the professional world as a consultant after graduation.</bio>
		<position>Consultant</position>
		<linkedin>http://www.linkedin.com/pub/mason-wrolstad/39/42/6b9</linkedin>
		<imagethumb>MasonW.jpg</imagethumb>
	</person>
</people>